Allied forces! Let's take shelter in the castle for now!
أيها الحلفاء، احتموا داخل القلعة حالًا
All right, hurry up!
حسنًا، لنسرع
Yeah, I wanna go in!
أجل، أريد الدخول إليها
Fire Tank Pirates! Cover them!
يا قراصنة فاير تانك، قوموا بتغطيتهم
– Rero ! – Yes, sir!
حاضر
Damn!
سحقًا
Bege! I saw it with my own eyes!
بيجي، رأيت ما فعلته بأم عيني
I can't believe you were plotting to assassinate Mama!
لا أصدّق أنّك كنت تخطط لاغتيال ماما
Was that his plan from the very beginning?!
أكان هذا ما يسعى إليه منذ البداية؟
Get inside the castle-rero !
أدخلوا إلى القلعة-ريرو
Rook: Cannon Preparation!
القلعة: إعداد المدافع
Cannon Firing!
إطلاق المدافع
So cool!
مذهل
It's a robot! A robot castle!
روبوت، إنّها قلعة آلية
How can you be excited at a time like this?!
كيف تكون منبهرًا في وقتٍ كهذا؟
How long can we hold out?
لكن، إلى متى سنصمد؟
This is killing my eardrums!
ستنفجر طبلة أذني
Mochi ?
موتشي؟
Is that...
...ذلك
the Tamate Box?!
صندوق تاماتي
All right!
عظيم
Big Brother!
أخي
He's gonna kill me!
سيقتلني
Big Brother! Thank you!
أخي، شكرًا لك
Let's go!
هيّا بنا
I won't let you go!
لن أدعكم تهربون
Cover them-rero ! Hurry-rero !
ساندوهم بسرعة-ريرو
Nami!
نامي
I'll squeeze you to death!
سأعصرك حتّى الموت
Nami-san !
نامي-سان
Nami!
نامي
We're gonna fight you!
نحن من سيُقاتلك
Ouch, ouch! It's hot!
مؤلم، مؤلم، مؤلم
You won't get away now!
لا مفرّ لكم بعد الآن
Chobro!
تشونيكي
Jinni!
جني
Let's go, Germa 66!
هيّا بنا يا جيرما 66
You annoying bastards!
أيها المزعجون الأوغاد
All of you, burn to death!
ستهلكون حرقًا جميعكم
I-Is that...?!
أ-أذلك؟
Germa's science.
تكنولوجيا جيرما العلمية
So that's what their memory armor looks like! It's even flameproof!
تلك هي دروع الذاكرة التشكيلية المضادة للنيران
I'll just immobilize them with my candy again!
سأقيّدهم بالحلوى خاصتي مجدّدًا
Candy Wave!
موج الحلوى
You obnoxious fleas!
أيتها الحشرات البغيضة
You're pretty big, but that doesn't mean you're tough.
رغم ضخامة جسدك إلّا أنّك لست بتلك القوة
Nami-san !
نامي-سان
Are you guys okay?!
هل أنتم بخير؟
I am!
أجل
Sanji-kun !
سانجي-كن
I'm glad that you're okay, Nami-san !
يسعدني أنّكِ بخير يا نامي-سان
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Jet Whip!
السوط النفاث
Luffy!
لوفي
– Hurry up! – This way!
هيّا أسرعوا
We should retreat as well-rero !
يجب أن نتراجع نحن أيضًا-ريرو
Well, well, this is the Tamate Box, a legendary hidden treasure.
ها هو الكنز الأسطوري الخفي؛ صندوق تاماتي
Nobody will see me this far away from the action! I love the current chaotic situation!
أنا بعيد بشكل كافٍ ولا أحد يستطيع رؤيتي بفضل تلك الفوضى
I'll take this opportunity to replace what's inside...
سأستغل هذه الفرصة لاستبدال ما بداخله
This is our last chance!
هذه فرصتنا الأخيرة
Cannon Firing!
إطلاق المدافع
Damn!
سحقًا
Candy Wall!
جدار الحلوى
Perospero!
بيروسبيرو
Oh, that hurts...
...كم هذا مؤلم
So is Germa working with you, too?
الجيرما في صفكم إذًا؟
I hope you bastards are ready for what's coming to you.
استعدوا لما هو آتِ أيها الأوغاد
You won't be laughing for long!
لن تدوم لحظات فرحك طويلًا
Rook: Movement!
تحرك القلعة
We'll shoot her in the back until we're out of ammo!
سأرديها من الخلف بكامل ذخيرتي
Time to die, Big Mom!
فلتموتي يا بيغ مام
Cannon...
إطلاق
Firing!
المدافع
What just happened?!
ما الذي حدث؟
Father, our left-side cannons were destroyed!
فاذر، دُمرّت جميع مدافع الميسرة
And the rest of them have been jammed with mochi !
وبقية مدافع القلعة محشوة بالموتشي
We can't fire them anymore!
لا يمكننا الإطلاق
K-Katakuri!
كـ-كاتاكوري
I've got some bad news for everyone in the castle...
لديّ إعلان لجميع من في القلعة
Big Father's limbs are trapped under candy!
عجلات بيغ فاذر مقيّدة بالحلوى
We can't even move anymore!
ولم يعد بوسعنا التحرّك
We're surrounded by Emperor Big Mom's pirate crew
نحن محاصرون من قبل طاقم قراصنة الإمبراطورة بيغ مام
and must now hole ourselves up in the castle while we're under siege!
ولا خيار أمامنا سوى خوض معركة يائسة تحت هذا الحصار
No...
...محال
Anyone who steps out will die.
...سنقتل كل من يخرج
Just come out already!
اخرجوا بسرعة
How could you let them use you like that?
كيف سمحتِ لهم باستغلالك لهذه الدرجة؟
I-I'm the victim here, Big Brother!
إنني ضحية يا أخي
Just hurry up and destroy each and every one of them!
أسرع بالقضاء عليهم جميعًا
Poison? That woman is quite troublesome...
سم؟ تلك المرأة صعبة المراس
There you are!
ظهرت
You're amazing, Bege! You're able to transform into a huge castle!
أنت رائع يا بيجي، لم أعرف أنّك تستطيع التحول إلى قلعة ضخمة
The Castle-Castle Fruit is so cool!
فاكهة القلعة مذهلة
This isn't the time for praise! Think about the situation we're in!
هذا ليس وقت الفرح، حريّ بكما أن تفكرا بمأزقنا الحالي
Dammit...
سحقًا
We planned this assassination for over a year,
خطة الاغتيال التي عملنا عليها لأكثر من سنة قد باءت بالفشل
We've never failed to assassinate someone before...
هذه أول مرة نفشل في اغتيال أحدٍ ما
In the end, an emperor proved to be out of our league...
هذا يثبت الفرق الشاسع بيننا وبين الأباطرة
What should we do now?
ما العمل الآن؟
We don't have much time left. Here's why.
ليس لدينا متسعٌ من الوقت، وسأخبركم بالسبب
Listen carefully, you guys!
أصغوا إليّ جميعًا
I am this castle. It's strong, but it isn't invincible.
هذه القلعة تمثّل جسدي رغم صلابتها إلّا أنّها ليست منيعة
If the castle gets destroyed, I die. Which means the castle disappears,
سأموت إن دمروا القلعة، وبعدها ستتلاشى
and then all of you will be tossed out there to be the prey for those monsters!
وبمجرّد خروجكم منها، سينقض عليكم الوحوش لافتراسكم
Prey?!
افتراسنا؟
I'll never forgive them...
لن أغفر لهم
Mama!
ماما
I can feel Mama's anger...
إنني أشعر بغضب ماما
It's hell out there, and it's hell in here.
أنتم هالكون لا محالة سواءً بقيتم أو خرجتم
We're in dire straits!
نحن في مأزق عويص
Don't blame me, Bege! Those launchers featured state-of-the-art, world-class...
لا تلمني يا بيجي، كانت تلك القاذفات هي الأكثر تطورًا في العالم
– W-What was that? – Father!
ما كان ذلك؟
Could it be...
...هذا
Look outside!
من الخارج
What?
ماذا؟
Outside?
الخارج؟
You bastards!
أنتما
Come out!
اخرجا
Bege!
بيجي
Straw Hat!
قبعة القش
I'm scared!
هذا مخيف
Big Mom came to her senses!
استعادت بيغ مام وعيها
All of you, come out of the castle!
اخرجوا جميعًا من القلعة
Show yourselves, you cowards!
أظهروا أنفسكم
Honey!
عزيزي
Father!
فاذر
So you betrayed me?
...إذًا فقد خنتنا
Bege!
يا بيجي؟
Honey! Stay with me!
تماسك يا عزيزي
I'm scared!
هذا مخيف، هذا مخيف، هذا مخيف، هذا مخيف
Come out, Bege! Straw Hat!
اخرجا يا بيجي وقبعة القش
Bege!
بيجي
Hold Pez!
اعتنِ ببيز
Come out!
اخرجا
Mama! It's me! Bege is my husband! We had a child together!
هذه أنا يا ماما، بيجي هو زوجي ولدينا طفل
Please just forgive him and let us go!
أرجو أن تغفري فعلته
Chiffon!
شيفون
You still look just like Lola!
إنّكِ لا تقلين شبهًا عن لولا كعادتك
She's going to attack!
ستهاجم
Watch out!
احترسي
Get back, Chiffon!
تراجعي يا شيفون
Madam!
سيدتنا
Mama! Please!
أرجوكِ يا ماما
I told you not to show that face around here!
سبق أن أخبرتك ألّا تظهري وجهك أمامي
That was close...
كان ذلك وشيكًا
Are you okay?
هل أنتِ بخير؟
Madam!
سيدتنا
Are you in on this assassination plot too, Chiffon?!
هل أنتِ متواطئة معهم في مخطط اغتيالي يا شيفون؟
You won't live to eat tomorrow's snacks, that's for sure!
لن تعيشي لتشهدي يوم الغد
Mama!
ماما
If she tears down the castle and Bege dies, then they'll all appear right in front of us!
عندما تتحطم القلعة ويهلك بيجي سيُقذف الجميع للخارج
Don't let a single one of them escape!
لا تدعوا أحدًا يلوذ بالفرار
The Fire Tank Pirates... the Straw Hat crew...
قراصنة فاير تانك، وقراصنة قبعة القش
Plus, Jinbe and Germa 66!
بالإضافة إلى جينبي وجيرما 66
They ruined the wedding and the tea party!
أفسدوا الزفاف وحفلة الشاي
I can't believe they underestimated us.
لا أصدق أنّهم استهانوا بنا لهذه الدرجة
We need to wring them out and make an example of them to the world.
لنشنقهم ونجعلهم عبرة للآخرين
Are you okay?
أأنت بخير؟
Damn, that old bag!
سحقًا لتلك العجوز الشمطاء
Big Father can take a cannon blast without a scratch,
رغم أنّ المدافع لا تقوى على خدش بيغ فاذر
but it can't defend against her!
إلّا أنّه عاجز أمامها
I've gotta go out there and kick her ass!
يجدر بي الخروج وإبراحها ضربًا
No, Luffy!
كلا يا لوفي
Chopper, grab him!
تشوبر، أوقفه
Okay!
مفهوم
What the?! Hey! Let go of me!
ماذا؟ أفلتني
Hey, Chopper! Let go of me!
تشوبر، أفلتني
Luffy! Don't get carried away!
لوفي، لا يجدر بك القتال
We're here to get Sanji-kun back, remember?!
أتينا لاستعادة سانجي-كن، أليس كذلك؟
We got the poneglyph copies we needed,
كما أننا نسخنا البونغليف
and we even helped Sanji-kun rescue his family!
وحققنا رغبة سانجي-كن بإنقاذ أفراد عائلته
We've completed our mission!
لقد أنجزنا جميع أهدافنا
Instead of fighting, you should be helping us come up with an escape plan!
إن كان لديك وقتًا للقتال، فيحسن بك أن تفكّر بحلٍّ للهرب
If we intended on fighting her, we would've brought Zoro and the rest! Isn't that right?!
كنا سنحضر زورو والآخرين لو أننا أردنا القتال، ألستُ محقة؟
Luffy-san, Nami-san is right.
لوفي-سان، إنّ نامي-سان محقة
We made it this far because we came in such a small group.
بلغنا هذا الحد بفضل قلة عددنا
Let's escape and meet up with Zoro-san and the others in Wano!
لنخرج بسلام ونلحق زورو-سان إلى بلاد وانو
Bege!
بيجي
Father!
فاذر
See?! Bege is...
انظروا إلى حالة بيجي
What should we do then?!
إذًا ما العمل؟
Bege is risking his life for us!
بيجي يتلقى كل الهجمات بدلًا منا
Dammit...
سحقًا
My plans are in utter ruin...
نحن لم نحقق أهدافنا على عكسكم
so I'm definitely not willing to sit idly by as you all relish in your success!
لن أقف ساكنًا وأشاهدكم تستمتعون بنجاحكم
Wait a minute, Bege-san ! You can't drag us down with you!
تريّث رجاءً يا بيجي-سان، لا يمكنك إقحامنا معك
I did what I was supposed to do!
وأنا فعلت ما هو مطلوب منّي
Give me back my heart this instant!
لذا أعد قلبي حالًا
Drag you down...?
إقحامكم؟
That's not a bad idea.
إنّها فكرة جيّدة
Like I said from the start, I don't care what happens to any of you guys!
فأنا لا أكترث لأمركم منذ البداية
But...
لكن أتباعي الأعزاء موجودون في هذا المكان
and my beloved wife and son are here.
وكذلك زوجتي وطفلي
And there's no way I can let them die!
لن أدعهم يموتون
Honey!
عزيزي
Father!
فاذر
Bege!
بيجي
There's only one way...
...لينجوا الجميع
to make sure everyone survives!
ثمة سبيلٌ وحيد
Only one?!
سبيلٌ وحيد؟
What is it?!
ما هو؟
Come out!
اخرجوا
I'm gonna destroy it!
سأدمر القلعة فوق رؤوسكم
It won't last much longer...
لن تصمد طويلًا
Get ready to attack anytime now...
استعدوا للهجوم في أية لحظة
I can crush them with this!
سأسحقهم بقبضتي هذه
Let's get rid of...
لنتخلص منهم جميعًا
Hurry up and come out! Then, I'll trap all of you in my mirror dimension!
أسرعوا بالخروج حتّى أحبسكم في عالم المرايا
The only way to survive... That is...
...السبيل الوحيد للنجاة هو
Hey!
أنت
Don't panic!
لا تذعروا
No matter how much I'm attacked...
مهما كانت ضراوة الهجوم الذي نتلقّاه
if Big Father leans or falls over,
وسواءً تعثر بيغ فاذر أو سقط
I'm the only one who will get hurt.
فأنا الوحيد الذي سيتلقى الضرر
As long as you guys are here, you won't get hurt at all.
لن تتأثروا ما دمتم في الداخل
– Come to think of it... – It's only Bege-san who is suffering.
...بذكر هذا
We can hear Big Mom's voice...
يمكننا سماع صراخ بيغ مام
but it's still calm in here.
لكن المكان هادئ في الداخل
That's right...
هذا ما أرمي إليه
And that won't change even if I change back into my human form.
ولن يختلف الأمر بعودتي لهيئتي البشرية
Listen... I'm going to return to being human with you all still inside!
اسمعوا، سأعود إلى هيئتي البشرية مع إبقائكم في الداخل
Then, Caesar will pick me up and fly us to safety!
بعدها سيحلّق بي سيزار بعيدًا للهرب
If all goes well, we'll get out of this mess.
إن سار الأمر كما ينبغي، فسننجو من هذه الورطة
Hey! How dare you try and put my life in danger without even asking me, you bastard!
أنت، كيف لك تعريض حياتي للخطر من دون سؤالي حتّى أيها الوغد؟
That's a suicide mission!
إنّها خطة انتحارية
They'll pump us full of lead as soon as we leave! That plan's chance of success is zero!
سيقضون علينا فور خروجنا، فرصة النجاح معدومة
Many of them use armanent haki!
كما أنّه ثمة العديد من مستخدمي هاكي التسلّح
Even if I turn into gas, I can't defend against them!
لا فائدة من التحول لهيئتي الغازية
Let me ask you something.
دعني أطرح عليك سؤالًا
Sanji,
يا سانجي
why did you save us?
لِمَ أنقذتنا؟
We're your enemies that fell right into their trap!
نحن ألد أعدائك وقد وقعنا في مكيدتهم
Because my father would be sad...
لأنّ أبي سيغمره الحزن
if I were still fixated on the hatred from my childhood...
إن عرف أنني ما زلت حاقدًا حيال ما حدث في طفولتي
Please let me out!
أخرجني يا أبي
I'm sorry that I was born weak!
أعتذر على ولادتي ضعيفًا
Help me, Dad!
أنقذني يا أبي، أنقذني يا أبي
He would be astonished that I had turned into such a small man
سيخيب أمله بي إن أصبحت وضيعًا يراقب موت عائلته الحقيقية باستمتاع مثلكم
Don't catch a cold.
لا تُصب بالبرد
I don't want to live a life where I'll be too ashamed
لا أرغب في عيش حياتي وأنا أشعر بالعار من مواجهته
Don't ever admit that I'm your father...
...حقيقة أنني والدك
to even a single person!
إيّاك والإقرار بها أمام الناس
I do not want anyone to learn of my shame!
إنّه عارٌ لا أريد لأحدٍ أن يعرف بشأنه
Do you understand?
أفهمت؟
Thirteen years ago,
قبل 13 سنة، فينسموك سانجي الذي هرب من جيرما قد لقي حتفه في البحر
And that is what you wanted.
أليس هذا ما أردته؟
So admit it!
...لذلك اعترف
You are not my father, Vinsmoke Judge!
بأنّك لست والدي يا فينسموك جادج
Don't ever show your face around us again!
إيّاك أن تريني وجهك مجدّدًا
I understand.
فهمت
I will never approach you...
بأنني لن أقترب منك
or the East Blue ever again!
أو من الأزرق الشرقي
I already did my part!
لقد نفّذتُ واجبي بالفعل
This wasn't part of the deal!
أما الباقي فهو ليس من ضمن اتفاقنا
If you don't do this, you're going to die anyway, Caesar!
إن لم تنفّذ ذلك، فستموت أيضًا يا سيزار
Open the gate!
افتح البوابة
Gang Bege! Until Caesar Clown carries you to safety through the air,
غانغ بيجي، حتّى تهرب أنت سيزار كلاون عبر السماء
Germa will serve to guard you!
نحن الجيرما سنوفر لكم الحماية
W-Wait a minute!
ا-انتظر قليلًا
What gives you the right to decide what I should do?!
لِمَ تُملي عليّ الأوامر؟
Your high-handed attitude hasn't changed, Judge!
أسلوبك المتعالي لم يتغيّر يا جادج
Oh yeah... Germa can fly, too.
هكذا إذًا، يمكنكم الطيران أيضًا يا أفراد جيرما
Then... we'll leave you behind.
إذًا سنترككم خلفنا هنا
That won't be a problem.
لا أمانع ذلك
All right, if we're trying to buy time, I'll...
...عظيم، إن كنا بحاجة إلى كسب الوقت، فسوف
There's no need, Luffy.
دعهم يتكفلون بالأمر يا لوفي
But...
...ولكن
I do not need help from a failure!
لا أحتاج مساعدة من فاشل
This is how they want to make amends.
يريدون تسوية الأمر بهذه الطريقة
Wait, wait! Whoa-whoa!
مهلًا، مهلًا، أنت
I never said I'd help, you fools!
لم أوافق على ذلك أيها الحمقى
Caesar!
سيزار
Shut up and do it!
اخرس ونفّذ
Ouch!
مؤلم
You'll pay for this!
ستندم على ذلك
Come on out already!
اخرجوا حالًا
Bege!
بيجي
Germa! Commence the attack!
جيرما، ابدؤوا الهجوم
Inside Big Father
داخل بيغ فاذر